

ABOUT ME

28 years old Argentinean hardware technician, full stack developer, technology passionate and coffee enthusiast. On the way of discovering a passion for the wonderful world of frontend. I love giving life to designs and the sense of acomplishment of a great UI!

SOCIALS

LinkedIn: /memmalopez

GitHub: /marcoselopez

Instagram: @emmanuelok29

LANGUAGES

SPANISH

ENGLISH

SOFT SKILLS

- Initiative
- Results Oriented
- Active Hearing
- Team Player
- Time Management

OTHER **KNOWLEDGES**

- Ionic React
- VuelS
- Vuex Pinia
- Redux
- SCRUM Methodolgy

MARCOS EMMANUEL LÓPEZ

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



Gobernador Fernando Riera 260, Las Talitas, Tucumán, 4101, Argentina



+54 (0381) 156675480



emmanuel.m.lopez@gmail.com

SKILLS

HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT REACTIS ANGULAR NODEIS MONGODB EXPRESSIS

EDUCATION

ROLLINGCODE SCHOOL

Tucumán 2021

Full Stack MERN Developer

- Frontend + Backend development focused on Javascript language and it's frameworks.
- Full application and best practices of agile methodology in group works.
- Use and best practices of Slack, GitHub, Trello, Mural, etc.

COLEGIO SANTO TOMA5

Tucumán 2010

Bachelor's Degree

 High school Bachelor's degree on a local school of my province.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFRECOM

Tucumán Mar 2022 - Present

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

Tucumán Sep 2021 - Present

NOROESTE NUTRICIÓN S.R.L.

Tucumán Apr 2021 - Mar 2022

Front End Developer

- Participation on the creation and maintenance of different projects using several frontend frameworks and libraries for clients of the company.

Front End Developer

 Web development using HTML, CSS, Javascript and Bootstrap on some small langin page projects.

Web development using React as main library on some bigger projects.

IT Manager

- In charge of IT on different areas of the company.
- Monitoring, maintenance and reparation of hardware, LAN and WLAN networks, VOIP services, etc.
- Responsible of the correct functioning of the company on an IT level on it's everyday routine.

IT, Data and Technical Support Manager

- In charge of IT and technical support of different clients of the company.
- Installation and configuration of different management, billing and stock softwares.
- Handling and configuration of hardware from different brands like Mikrotik, Ubiquiti, HP, etc.
- Implementation of IP PBXs based on Asterisk technology. Configuration of FXO, FXS and GSM hardwares on brands like Dinstar, Synway, GrandStream, etc.
- Implementation and configuration of network structures through cable, wireless (Ubiquiti's Rockets, Powerbeams, Litebeams, etc.) or optic fiber (including OLT's and GPON's from different brands).
- Installation, configuration and maintenance of CCTV systems from different brands like Hikvision, Dahua, GrandStream, etc.

CONNET S.R.L.

Tucumán May 2017 - Apr 2021